One -egg twins are our natural clones.
They have similarity in DNA.
They have the same heritage you can say.
Because one -egg twins are more equal than two -egg twins
Then we interpret as that there is something that is hereditary behind psychopathy.
We measure psychopathy at twin 1 and twin 2 in one -egg twins.
And twin 1 and twin 2 in two -egg twins.
And then we are happy to study thousands of such twin pairs.
And then we see that one -egg twins are more similar in psychopathic features than two -egg twins.
Then it does not answer the question:
What is hereditary then?
How does it work?
How does it work that we actually see something hereditary behind psychopathy?
And of course it is important to be aware of.
Especially when we talk about how to handle it.
And how to diagnose it right and what treatment is required.
General one can say about people with psychopathy and their crime
that it tends quite rarely, just like criminals in general,
To be quite versatile.
Rather than specialized.
I think many people believe based on the media image that many who commit crimes
are very specialized and niche.
We see many serial killers in TV series and movies.
Serial killer is a disappearance of people who commit crimes.